I call glp1 medications a miracle drug
and I've said that before it is the most
important medical breakthrough since the
invention of penicillin because what's
killing us now it's metabolic disease so
we need tools for this the same way that
in the 1940s infectious diseases were
killing us we needed a tool antibiotics
so now gp1s are becoming a tool it's not
the Allin answer it's not a Panacea but
it's an important tool
why we know it is such an important
medication because it is affecting our
economic behavior our our our the way we
consume everything around us so big food
big alcohol and big farma don't like
those medications because fast food
industry are seeing a decrease in their
numbers for patient on patients who take
glp1 there was a study that was done by
Walmart who showed that people who take
glp1 tend to have less junk that they're
buying at their stores there was another
study that the CEO of nestle came out
and said that patients who take gp1
don't want to use our products we need
to watch that so it's affecting our
consumer Behavior which other medication
have you ever heard that they're talking
about it on Wall Street the ACE
inhibitors no matter how important that
Discovery was it did not affect what we
buy it did not affect our economic
behavior um cancer medication now the
big talk is on CT the immunotherapy it's
a it's a MAG magic medication but it's
not affecting our economic behavior so
how interesting is it that now a
medication can change not only our
health care it will change our consumer
Behavior big food and big farmers afraid
of this because now those medications
are giving back people the power not to
be addicted to those horrible foods and
interesting enough again with the Maha
movement right now in the US they just
bend red Dy number three and I
celebrated that but this is only one
toxin out of thousands red dye number 40
is still in use and it's been shown to
have so many problems um you know
there's a concept called the obesogens
obesogens are the toxins that affect our
metabolism um metabolism and cause
increase fatty liver decrease of our
metabolism and increase body weight
increase body fat and one of the most
common uh toxins that that have strong
relationships with this is those pias
those per or polyl alculated substances
that are found in everything from
clothing to Teflon on our cookware and
almost everywhere recent studies show
that 97% of Americans have high levels
of pfas in their in their systems and it
is associated with with obesity um
difficulty losing or regaining weight
easier and fatty lever only one just
this PFA is also associated with high
risk of cancer developmental disorders
testosterone issues and reproductive
issues 97% of Americans have that in
their blood microplastics Plastics are
basic
estrogen microplastic was found in
almost 100% of testicular tissues that
they've that they've checked so we see a
society that is filled with endocrine
disrupting chemicals and we're seeing
this endocrine epidemic that we're
seeing with everything with metabolic
disease reproductive disease low
testosterone and infertility and cancer
we need to change things so I need
generals like RFK Jr and the big big
people who can talk to the Senate and to
the government but in the meantime me as
the food Soldier you as the food Soldier
Will work with one patient at a time and
make them healthy one by one
[Music]